# CINDY PHAM

DESIGNER + ART DIRECTOR



## **PROFILE**

Cindy Pham is a designer & art director who specializes in design strategy, brand development, and user interface and experience. The roots of her passion stem from her fascination with storytelling through visual arts and interactive digital experiences. Her work has also earned her a spot on the jury panel for Awwwards and the FWA.

#### RECOGNITION

2017 ADC Merit Award

2017 Silver ADDY Award

2017 Webby Awards Honoree

2016 Design Student Spotlight

Awwwards - Site of the Day

FWA - Site of the Day

Press: AdWeek

Press: Fast Company

Press: Mashable

## **SELECTED CLIENTS**

Google, Adidas, Adult Swim, Spotify,

Oxygen TV, Pinterest, ŌURA Ring,

Downtown Norfolk Council, UC Davis

## **EXPERIENCE**

January 2018 - Present

Awwwards | Design Judge

Serving on the design jury panel for Awwwards, a professional web design and development competition that recognizes and promotes the best of innovative web design.

June 2016 - Present

**Grow** | Art Director

Working in an award-winning digital agency to design intelligent and engaging interactive experiences for a wide range of client types and target platforms, including Google, Adidas, Spotify, and Adult Swim.

October 2017 - January 2018

The FWA | Judge

Served on a jury panel for the FWA, which showcases the most progressive and forward-thinking projects created by individuals, agencies, and brands.

## **EDUCATION**

2012 - 2016

Design, B.A.

University of California, Davis

#### **CONTACT**

Website | cindypham.com

**Email** | cindycancreate@gmail.com

**Phone** | 408 406 7449